A Guide to the Office of the Provost, University of Virginia, University History Officer, [1961-1979]
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Provost, University of Virginia, University History Officer [1961-1979]
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-3/5/1.791 and 901
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library.
Contents List
- RG-3/5/1.791
  - General Correpsondence 1969-1976
  - General Correpsondence 1977-1979, n.d.
  - Barringer, Anna Maria, Pleasant to Remember[1969-1974]
  - Budget 1976-1978
  - Facilities 1975-1979
  - Founders Day 1976
  - Inaugural Committees, Frank Loucks Hereford 1974-1975
  - Indian Massacre of 1622 1976
  - McConnell, James Rogers; Portrait 1977
  - Printed Material re: University History n.d.
  - Shannon Garden 1978
  - Southampton n.d.
- RG-3/5/1.901
  - Virginia Dabney[1961-1979]
  - Virginia History and Museums Federation (2 folders) [1979]